(
"ai_sub_version": "2.9.1",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 7,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 15,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true
),
"gemini_cli": (
"timeout": 600,
"overwrite_system_prompt": false
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch"
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"run": 5,
"max": 5,
"delay": 30
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false
)
えー、皆様。
Uh, everyone...
本日は、轟はじめ生誕祭2026...
Today, for Todoroki Hajime's Birthday 2026...
「Rise in Motion」に...
live stream "Rise in Motion"...
お越しくださいまして、誠にありがとうございます！
thank you very much for coming!
えー、開演に先立ちまして、皆様にお願いとご案内を申し上げます。
Prior to the show starting, I have a few requests and announcements for you.
えー、当配信は一部収録を含みますが、
Now, while parts of this stream are pre-recorded,
生配信部分もございますので、
there are also live segments,
いっぱいコメントして盛り上げてください！
so please leave lots of comments and help build the hype!
今もね、ぶわーっていっぱい、おお、こんちくわ、きちゃ！
Right now, they're pouring in! "Oh," "Konchikuwa," "It's here!"
パチパチと、ありがとうございます！
And clapping too. Thank you so much!
えー、当配信のハッシュタグは、「#轟はじめ生誕祭2026」です。
The hashtag for this stream is #TodorokiHajimeBirthday2026.
SNSでたくさんポストしていただけると嬉しいです。
I'd be happy if you could post a lot about it on social media.
えー、開演中はね、カメラやスマートフォンなどによる写真撮影大歓迎なので、
During the show, taking photos with cameras or smartphones is highly encouraged,
たこさんポストして盛り上げていただけると幸いです。
so please post a lot of them and help generate excitement!
それでは、開演までしばらくお待ちください。
Well then, please wait a little longer until the show begins.
えー、皆様。
Uh, everyone...
本日は、轟はじめ生誕祭2026...
Today, for Todoroki Hajime's Birthday 2026...
「Rise in Motion」に...
live stream "Rise in Motion"...
お越しくださいまして、誠にありがとうございます！ パート2！
thank you very much for coming! Part 2!
どれ？ どれか？
Let's see... Is there any?
なんか、ぐるぐるしてなさそうですね、皆様。
It doesn't seem like anyone's stream is buffering, everyone.
おおって、わくわく、こんちくわと。大丈夫そうです。
I see "Oh," "Excited," and "Konchikuwa." It looks like we're good.
えー、開演に先立ちまして、皆様にお願いとご案内を、ちょっともう一回申し上げます。
Prior to the show starting, let me repeat the requests and announcements once more.
えー、当配信は一部収録を含みますが、
Now, while parts of this stream are pre-recorded,
生配信部分もございますので、
there are also live segments,
いっぱいコメントして盛り上げていただけると嬉しいです。
so I'd be happy if you'd leave lots of comments and get excited!
きちゃ！大丈夫そパート2きちゃ！ありがとう！
It's here! Part 2 of "Seems okay" is here! Thank you!
えー、今日の配信のハッシュタグは、ハッシュタグ『#おはしの生誕祭2026』です。
The hashtag for today's stream is #OhashiNoSeitansai2026.
SNSでたくさんポストしてください。
Please post a lot on social media.
えー、公演中は
During the performance...
カメラやスマートフォンなどによる写真撮影、大歓迎です！
Taking photos with cameras or smartphones is highly welcome!
たくさんポストして、盛り上げていただけると嬉しいです！
I'd be happy if you post a lot and hype things up!
それでは
And now,
開演まで
until the show starts,
今しばらくお待ちください！
please wait just a little longer!
ワンタイム無能な絵の具に
One-time, with useless paints,
くだらない紛い物だってボラリアップ
even worthless counterfeits, Volari-up!
喝采消し去るようなもん
It's like erasing the applause,
おちょくりピエロながら僕は吠える
playing the teasing clown, I howl.
才能のワザはどうにかしまっちゃってるけど
Though my talented tricks are somehow packed away,
感性はノーだっての
my sensitivity says "no."
愛に侵された言葉の心拍数
The heart rate of words afflicted by love,
生きていくたび胸は沈んでいく<
each time I live, my chest sinks.
どうなってんだろなプロドラッグ
What's going on, pro-drug?
揺れるの？
Is it shaking?
愛想売ってもしょうがねえ
It's no use selling smiles,
明日から稼ぐお金はどんだけ？
how much money will I make from tomorrow?
あーだこーだそんなもんか
Blah blah, is that all?
うるせえわな
Shut up.
ワンタイム無能な絵の具に
One-time, with useless paints,
絡まっていく脳を満たしてくれ
please fill my tangled brain.
未来の想像なんか描けない
I can't draw any imagination of the future,
くだらない紛い物だってそれ
even a worthless counterfeit, that's it.
半端モノなら洒落にならないじゃん
If it's half-baked, it's no laughing matter, right?
お代わりおねだりして僕は思い通り
Begging for seconds, I get my way.
退屈ですぐまた罵詈雑言インベーダー
Bored, and soon again, abuse-spewing invaders,
足が止まってる秀才さん
the prodigy who has stopped in their tracks,
死にそうでもギリギリですか？
are you at your limit even if you look like you're dying?
のらりくらり躱すわ
I'll dodge lazily,
はじめまして神様
nice to meet you, God.
もし救われるのなら歩き切るわ今から
If I am to be saved, I'll walk all the way from now on.
Get down Get down 揺らめいて
Get down, get down, swaying,
乗り込んだスニーカーが君を狂わしてんだ
the sneakers you stepped into are driving you crazy.
雨降ったらもうちょっと浮かぶかね
If it rains, will it float a bit more?
汗かいていく最後もあっけない
Sweating till the end, it's so abrupt.
どんな感触そんなもんさ虚しいわな
What kind of feeling, that's just how it is, how empty.
BANZAI
絵の具散り
Scattered paint...
からまわってテクノを満たしてくれ
spins around, satisfy me with techno.
未来予想図なんか描けない
I can't draw any blueprint for the future,
くだらない夢が彩るのだってそれ
because even trivial dreams color our lives.
半端ものならやれない マジじゃん
Half-baked people can't do it, seriously.
お分かりになってボスは思い通り
Once you understand, the boss gets their way.
ええじゃないか
Ee ja nai ka
パラリラここわきっと奈落だ
Para-rira, here must be hell
声にもならぬ声が
Voices that aren't even voices
腹の底からせり上がるんだ
Rising from the bottom of my stomach
「ダメ！それ！」押し殺す本能
'No! That!' Instinct I suppress
ユラユラ鈍色の海から
From the swaying dull-colored sea
幽列車と雲ヶ島
Ghost train and Cloud Island
ただただ君は呟くんだ
You're just muttering
「人は怖いね」と
'People are scary,' you say
今弾ける七色
Now the seven colors burst
アイアイ アイアイ
Ai-ai, ai-ai
宙を舞って踊り散らすの
Dancing and scattering in the air
ファッションビートで気取って
Acting cool with fashion beats
チンケな狂人ぶんじゃない
Don't act like a cheesy lunatic
報われない悲しみ食らってこう
Let's eat up the unrewarded sadness
ファッションビートに染まって
Stained by fashion beats
言うことないなら息しても
If you have nothing to say, even breathing
無駄だ アイヤ イヤイヤ
Is a waste, aiya iyaiya
笑え少年よ
Laugh, young boy
「ええじゃないか ええじゃないか
'Ee ja nai ka, ee ja nai ka'
この先は何にもわからんし
What lies ahead, I don't know at all
無礼じゃないか 無礼じゃないか」
Isn't it rude, isn't it rude?'
クソッタレ見てられん煩脳
Dammit, I can't stand this obsession
嗚呼 荒れ狂う世の中だから
Ah, because it's a rampaging world
アイアイ アイアイ
Ai-ai, ai-ai
宙を舞って終わりにすんの
Dancing in the air and ending it
ファッションビートで気取って
Acting cool with fashion beats
チンケな狂人ぶんじゃない
Don't act like a cheesy lunatic
報われない悲しみ食らってこう
Let's eat up the unrewarded sadness
ファッションビートに染まって
Stained by fashion beats
言うことないなら息しても
If you have nothing to say, even breathing
無駄だ アイヤ イヤイヤ
Is a waste, aiya iyaiya
笑え少年よ
Laugh, young boy
絵に描いたようなストーリー
The story drawn in a picture...
僕の色を塗れぬほどに落ちぶれた
I'm too fallen to paint my own colors.
モノクロに過ぎる日を
Monochrome passing days...
乗り越えられたら
if I can overcome them...
嗚呼 今夜は笑って
Ah, tonight I'll laugh
あの幽列車にキスをして
And kiss that ghost train
七色に生まれ変わるのさ
To be reborn in seven colors
ファッションビートに染まって
Stained by fashion beats
言うことないなら息しても
If you have nothing to say, even breathing
無駄だ アイヤ イヤイヤ
Is a waste, aiya iyaiya
笑え少年よ
Laugh, young boy
わぁー！楽しい！
Wow! That was fun!
はぁ、はぁ、やっぱり歌って踊るの楽しい！
Ah, ah... Singing and dancing is indeed so fun!
いぇーい！
Yay!
やっちゃ、ちょっとぶちかましちゃったんですけど、どうですか？
I did it! I went a bit wild, but how was it?
え？なんか番長とかやってたんですか？
Eh? Was I acting like a gang leader or something?
え？お？
Eh? Oh?
なん、なんすか？え、なんか撮ってました？
What, what is it? Eh, were you taking photos?
え、なんか撮ってましたよね？
Wait, you were taking photos, right?
え、てかなんか、これ配信されて、これ配信されてます？これ
Wait, is this... is this being streamed?! Is this streamed?!
ええー！
What?!
ちょ、ちょ、著作権とかあるんですけど、はしもにも！え、ちょっと...
Wait, wait! I have copyrights too, you know! Even for Hashimo! Wait, hang on...
なん、なんかコメントがすごい流れてるんですけど
Why are the comments scrolling so fast?
反転してて読めません！
They're flipped, so I can't read them!
えー、ちょ、なんかパチパチって拍手してくれてて
Um, wait, some are giving me a round of applause...
なんか「かっこよすぎ」って何？
What's this about me being "too cool"?
え、すごい、なんか、え？口、口、なんか口開けられた、え、なんか
Wait, amazing, like, what? Mouth, mouth, my mouth opened... Wait...
なんかありがとうございました！
Thank you so much anyway!
ハッシュタグ「#番長の生誕祭2026」ってなんかたくさんポストしてくれてるみたいなんですけど
It seems a lot of you are posting with the hashtag "#BanchosBirthday2026"...
なんなんだ、このタグは。分かんないけど
What is this tag? I don't really know, but...
はじめ、お祝いしてもらってるし、ポストしてもらったら嬉しいかも！
Since Hajime is being celebrated, I'd be happy if you made a post!
ありがとうございます！
Thank you!
えー、やっとはじめ、歌ったり踊ったりするの好きで
Um, after all, Hajime loves singing and dancing...
本当はこう、たくさんの人の前でパフォーマンスすることに憧れて
To tell the truth, I've always yearned to perform in front of many people...
ちょっと、上京したいな、とか思ってるんですけど、ちょっと勇気が出なくて
And I've been thinking of moving to Tokyo, but I couldn't build up the courage...
うーん、え？「はじめなら大丈夫」？「いける」？
Hmm, wait. "Hajime will be fine"? "You can do it"?
え、コメントの方はちょっとどう思ってる？
What do you guys in the comments think?
「かわいい」、「なんて？」、あ、なんか思ってた、あ、「ダンスうま！」
"Cute," "Say what?" Ah, what I was thinking... Ah, "Great dancer!"
すごい褒められてる！あ、「かっこいい！」、あ、褒められてる！
I'm being praised so much! Ah, "So cool!" Ah, they're praising me!
よし、じゃあ、皆さんにすごい勇気をもらったので、はじめ
Alright, now that I've gotten so much courage from all of you, Hajime...
行ってきます！夢を目指して、上京してくる！
is going! I'm going to move to Tokyo to pursue my dream!
ありがとう！
Thank you!
荒れ狂う季節の中を 二人は一人きり さらり
Inside the raging season, the two of us are all alone, refreshingly.
明け行く夕日の中を 今夜も昼下がり さらり
Inside the sunset that's starting to dawn, tonight too, it's after noon, refreshingly.
どれほど朽ち果てようと 最後にゃ笑いたい 何のために
No matter how much we rot away, I want to smile at the end. No matter what
戦おうとも 動機は愛がいい
I'm fighting for, my motivation should be love.
新しい日々は探さずとも常に ここに 色々見てきたけれど
Even if I don't look for new days, they are always right here. I've seen many things,
この瞳は永遠に きらり
but these eyes, forever, sparkle.
あれほど生きてきたけど 全ては夢みたい
I've lived through so much, but it all feels like a dream.
あれもこれも魅力的でも 私は君がいい
Everything is attractive, but I prefer you.
どこにいたの 探してたよ
Where were you? I was looking for you.
連れてって 連れてって
Take me with you, take me with you.
何もかも 捨ててくよ
I'll throw everything away.
荒れ狂う 季節の中も 群衆の中も
Even in the raging season, even in the crowd,
君とならば さらり さらり
if I'm with you, refreshingly, refreshingly.
新しい日々も 拙い過去も 全てがきらり
New days, and clumsy pasts, everything sparkles.
無くしてしまったものを振り返って ほろり
Looking back on the things I've lost, I tear up a little.
時には途方に暮れてただ風に吹かれて ゆらり
Sometimes I'm at a loss, just blown by the wind, swaying.
息せき切ってきたの 行き先は決めたの
I've been breathing hard, I've decided where to go.
迷わずに行きたいけど保証はしないよ
I want to go without hesitation, but I can't guarantee anything.
何か分かったようで 何も分かってなくて保存はしないよ
It feels like I've understood something, but I haven't understood anything.
やっと分かって本当に良かった
I'm so glad I finally understand.
新しい日々は探さずとも
Even if I don't look for new days,
常にここにある ここにある ここに ここに
they are always right here, right here, right here.
色々見てきたけれど
I've seen so many different things,
この瞳は永遠に他にはない 永遠にきらり
but these eyes are eternally like no other, eternally sparkling.
生きてこれたけど
I managed to live on, but...
全ては夢みたい
everything feels like a dream.
あれもこれも
This and that,
魅力的なのに
everything is so charming,
私は君がいい
but I only want you.
どこにいってたの
Where had you gone?
探してたよ
I was looking for you.
連れてって 連れてって
Take me away, take me away,
何もかも 捨てていくよ
I'll leave everything behind.
どこまでも どこまでも
No matter how far, no matter how far.
荒れ狂う季節の中も
Even in the midst of raging seasons,
群衆の中も
and in the middle of crowds,
君とならば さらり さらり
if I'm with you, it's so effortless.
新しい日々も
Even the new days,
拙い過去も
and my awkward past,
全てがきらり
everything shines so brightly.
SUPERNOVA
[On-Screen: SUPERNOVA]
welcome to our シアター ほら
Welcome to our theater, come on,
踊れば幕開けの合図が it's calling you back
if you dance, the signal of the curtain rising is calling you back.
月火から水木にお疲れ everybody clap your hands
Good job from Mon-Tue to Wed-Thu, everybody clap your hands.
待ち侘びた金土日さ come and bring all your friends
It's the long-awaited Fri-Sat-Sun, come and bring all your friends.
世間はwork work 目線はdon't stop
The world is work work, our eyes don't stop.
心も体もボロボロです
Both mind and body are completely worn out.
頑張り屋な日本人に everybody clap your hands
To the hardworking Japanese, everybody clap your hands.
やるせない朝にうんざりしちゃって
I've got so sick of those depressing mornings.
何もしないroutine 染み込んだ癖 mistake
Doing nothing routine, a deep-seated habit, mistake.
また自分のせいに
Blaming myself again.
憧れ持った能天気保存
With carefree longings,
結局はいつも通りだ
in the end, it's just like always.
過ぎ去っていくday by day
Passing by, day by day,
考えたってdon't know if it's the right way
even if I think about it, don't know if it's the right way.
吹く風も味方にして保存
Making even the blowing wind our ally,
let's ride away
welcome to ourシアター
Welcome to our theater.
ほら踊れば幕開けの合図が it's calling you back
Look, if we dance, the signal of the curtain rising is calling you back.
波瀾万丈な人生くらいがちょうどいいのさ
A life full of ups and downs is just about right.
君が創るショータイムを見せて見せてちょうだい保存
Show me, show me the showtime that you create!
春夏すぎ秋冬にやれやれ everybody clap your hands
Spring and summer pass, autumn and winter, oh dear, everybody clap your hands.
ギリギリ駆け込んで間に合うかの never ending game
Rushing in at the last second to see if we'll make it, a never ending game.
気持ちはgo go されどもno no
My heart says go go, but yet it's no no.
現実はそう甘くないね
Reality is not that sweet, is it?
働き屋な日本人に everybody clap your hands
To the hardworking Japanese, everybody clap your hands.
お決まりのsuit and tie how can i be myself and i
The usual suit and tie, how can I be myself and I?
どれもこれも色のない世界には興味ない
I have no interest in any of this colorless world.
見る向こう側で
On the other side of what we see,
we're gonna find a way
welcome to ourシアター
Welcome to our theater.
ほら踊れば幕開けの合図が it's calling you back
Look, if we dance, the signal of the curtain rising is calling you back.
波瀾万丈な人生くらいがちょうどいいのさ保存
A life full of ups and downs is just about right.
君が創るショータイムを見せて見せて
Show me, show me the showtime that you create.
過ぎ去っていくday by day
Passing by, day by day,
考えたってdon't know if it's the right way
even if I think about it, don't know if it's the right way.
吹く風も味方にして
Making even the blowing wind our ally,
let's ride away
welcome to ourシアター
Welcome to our theater.
ほら踊れば幕開けの合図が it's calling you back
Look, if we dance, the signal of the curtain rising is calling you back.
波瀾万丈な人生くらいがちょうどいいのさ
A life full of ups and downs is just about right.
君が創るショータイムを見せて見せてちょうだい
Show me, show me the showtime that you create!
とびっきりショータイム 誰でも招待
An extraordinary showtime, inviting everyone!
あなたのショータイムを見せてちょうだい
Please show me your showtime!
とびっきりショータイム 誰でも招待
An extraordinary showtime, inviting everyone!
あなたのショータイムを見せてちょうだい
Please show me your showtime!
あ、あの、星街すいせいちゃんのチャンネルですよね？
Ah, um, you're Hoshimachi Suisei-chan's channel, right?
ご存知かしら？ありがとう！
Do you know of her? Thank you!
え、あの、なんか、超偶然だったけど...
Eh, um, like, it was a total coincidence but...
一緒に歌えて嬉しかったりゅ！
I was so happy to sing with you!
私も嬉しかったわ。
I was happy too.
わぁ、嬉し！ありがとうございます！
Wow, I'm so glad! Thank you so much!
ありがとう。
Thank you.
え、でも、でもあの、このシアター勝手に入っているんですか？
Um, but... but are we allowed to just sneak into this theater?
まあ、ダメかもしれないわ。
Well, we might not be.
ダメなの！？
We're not?!
うん。
Yeah.
え、じゃ、怒られる、怒られる？
Wait, then are we gonna get in trouble? Get in trouble?
まあ、怒られるわ。
Well, we definitely are.
なんでここ連れてきてくれたんですか？
Then why did you bring me here?!
あそこの人がもう銃構えてるわ、こうやって。
That person over there is already aiming a gun at us like this.
怖い、怖い！
Scary, scary!
え、そんな物騒なもの持ってますか。
Wait, do they really have something so dangerous?
あ、違う違う、あの、この人、オーディション、しゅつ、しゅつ、しゅつじょうしゃ、オーディション、オーディション出場者で。
Ah, no no, um, this person is... audition... par- par- participant! An audition... audition participant!
え？
Eh?
ここオーディションやってるんで。オーディション出場者、これにしよう！ね？
They're holding auditions here. Let's say we're audition participants! Okay?
どういうこと？
What do you mean?
そういうこと、そういうこと。
Just go with it, go with it!
ここでオーディションやってるんだ。
So they are doing auditions here.
そうだよ。受けた方がいいんじゃない？ね？
That's right. You should audition too, right?
立ち去る？
To leave?
じゃなきゃ撃たれる、撃たれる。
Otherwise you'll get shot! You'll get shot!
怖い、怖いよ！
That's scary! I'm scared!
撃たれるよ、ねえ。
You'll get shot, you know.
あれ、星街すいせいじゃない！？
Wait, isn't that Hoshimachi Suisei?!
あ、あれ？あれ？あ！
Oh, wait. Oh? Ah!
あれ？
Wait...
いけねえ、じゃあねえ！
Oh crap, see ya!
ええ！？すいせいちゃん、やばい、ええ！？
What?! Suisei-chan, oh my god, what?!
あれ、ええ？
Huh, what?!
あれ？
What's going on?
どっちや？
Which way?
はぁ。
Sigh...
しーっ
Shh...
ステラきらり 2人だけの party party time
Stella glittering, a party party time for just the two of us
抜き足 差し足 荒く息潜め劇場
Stealthy steps, holding our rough breath in the theater
step by step, be night 教えるわ
Step by step, be night, I'll teach you
心の思うままに 踊り狂わせて
Let us dance like crazy, just as our hearts desire
強気な瞳 隠して そうして少し微笑んで
Hide your strong eyes, and then smile a little
上品に蹴り上げ 静かにちょっと豪快ダンス
Kick up elegantly, quiet yet slightly dynamic dance
仕留めてあげるわ決めるの
I'll finish you off
step light 同じダンスばかりじゃダメ
Step light, doing the same dance over and over won't do
feel like もう一人の自分に勝つの
Feel like, I'll win against my other self
dance 盗まれたら取り返すのが基本
Dance, if it's stolen, taking it back is the basic rule
tough 愛してバディーズ 静かに足音
Tough, love your buddies, quiet footsteps
ひらりと躱して猫の目 さらりと手には招待状
Lightly dodging like a cat's eye, smoothly holding an invitation in hand
華麗に無音の逃げ 静かにちょっと豪快ダンス
Splendidly escaping in silence, quiet yet slightly dynamic dance
仕留めてあげるわ
I'll finish you off
step light 互い感じ party party time
Step light, feeling each other, party party time
抜き足 差し足 荒く息潜め劇場
Stealthy steps, holding our rough breath in the theater
step by step, be night そのまま踊ってよ
Step by step, be night, just keep dancing like that
ステップついてきてね 踏み出してよ
Keep up with the steps, take a stride forward
ここで決めるの 誰も奪えやしないわ
We'll settle it here, no one can steal it away
胸に秘めてる法則と 静かに踊って
With the rules hidden in your chest, dance quietly
静かに踊ってよ ステップはお静かに
Dance quietly, keep your steps quiet
Switch 鏡に眩めJack 孤独カタカタそらご覧
Switch, dazzle Jack in the mirror, look at the rattling loneliness
Squeeze 冴えほら五感 かりそめの...
Squeeze, look, your five senses are clear, to this transient...
超お洒落な帽子とステッキを持てば
If you carry a super stylish hat and cane,
Step in 最後のLUNATIC すでに高揚主催Club Episode
Step in, the last lunatic, already in high spirits hosting a club episode.
さあ乾杯してバラッド 今はこの欲望に踊れよ
Now toast with a ballad, and dance in this greed right now.
有限なら夜が明ける前まで
If it's finite, before the night breaks,
味わい尽くすべき
we should savor it to the end.
You have a BAD HATTER
支配なるモンスター
An absolute master monster!
We are BAD HATTER
目線も体調もナンセンス
Even your gaze and condition are nonsense.
バンバン、ムーンライト
Bang, bang, moonlight!
十代のダンスフロア
A teenage dance floor.
We have a stakeholder
競争に飲まれ踊れ
get swallowed up by the competition and dance!
バリエーション ほら空中飛び交う金銀銅
Variations, look, gold, silver, and bronze flying through the air!
甲斐性ないなら平等さ 老いも若きも誰もが混ざり合う
If you have no resourcefulness, it's equal. Old, young, everyone mixes together.
Step in 最後のLUNATIC 誰も彼もが耳打ちトーク
Step in, the final lunatic, everyone and anyone whispering talk.
一緒にどうですお嬢さん 素顔を剥がした紳士がShall we dance
How about joining in, young lady? A gentleman with his mask off asks, "Shall we dance?"
揺らぐ灯火 どんな見た目だろうが
The flickering light, no matter what you look like,
気にする暇もない
there's no time to even care.
You have a BAD HATTER
支配なるモンスター
An absolute master monster!
We are BAD HATTER
目線も体調もナンセンス
Even your gaze and condition are nonsense.
バンバン、ムーンライト
Bang, bang, moonlight!
十代のダンスフロア
A teenage dance floor.
We have a stakeholder
競争に飲まれ踊れ
get swallowed up by the competition and dance!
ダバダバダバディディディドゥダバディビディビドゥドゥディディディドゥ
Dabadaba dabadididudabadibidibidududidididu...
ドゥビダバドゥディドゥダドゥドゥドゥドゥダドゥディダドゥダディディダドゥ
Dubidabadududadudududadudidadudadididadu...
ダバダバダバダバダバダバダバドゥダダダダダバダバダバダバダババドゥ
Dabadabadabadabadabadabadabudadadadabadabadabadabadababadu...
アラババドゥダラドゥダラディバジャバディダダディディダビダビディババディバドゥ
Alababadudaladudaladibajabadidadadadididabidibidibabadibadu...
You have a BAD HATTER
支配なるモンスター
An absolute master monster!
We are BAD HATTER
目線も体調もナンセンス
Even your gaze and condition are nonsense.
バンバン、ムーンライト
Bang, bang, moonlight!
十代のダンスフロア
A teenage dance floor.
We have a stakeholder
競争に飲まれ踊れ
get swallowed up by the competition and dance!
お、前チャック開いてるぞ 何持ってんの？
Oh, your zipper is open. What are you holding?
お？ バツ？
Oh? An X?
バツ？ え、バツってどういうこと？ も、もしかして...
An X? Wait, what do you mean by X? Could it be...
青衣ちゃんの審査員だったの？
Were you Aoihashi's judge?
だってさっき なんかノリノリでドゥビドゥバってやってたじゃん！
But earlier you were so into it, doing the scat thing!
お、退いてって？ なんなんだよ！
Oh, "move aside"? What's your problem?!
青衣頑張って... ちょっと、ちょっと退いてって。ねえ！
Aoihashi worked hard... Wait, "move aside a bit"? Hey!
あれ？
Huh?
なんか、体が動かないんだけど
For some reason... my body won't move...
う、動かない...
I can't... move...
なんか放したくてもダメみたいだ
It seems I can't let go of it even if I try...
なんだよこれ！ 願い下げだこんな... こんなシアター！ 退いて、退いてやる！
What is this?! I'm so done with... this theater! I'm leaving, I'll get out of here!
退いてって... チャック開いてるよ？
Saying "move aside"... is my zipper open?
なんなんだよ！ 見ちゃったじゃん！ 退け！
What is this?! You saw it! Move!
no thank you, alright? 能天気 どうかしている
No thank you, alright? You're optimistic, you've gone mad.
「不適切」「指摘には低姿勢で」正義し放題 mr. x 放火している
"Inappropriate," "Keep a low profile when pointed out," self-righteousness runs wild, Mr. X is setting fires.
「※真偽不明」なんて正気じゃない 夜は on and on and on
"*Truth unconfirmed," that's insane, the night goes on and on and on.
僕ら怨念飲んでへべれけじゃん
We're drinking up grudges and getting dead drunk.
目には？歯には?簡単だ 吸って吐いてジャッジメント
An eye for an eye, a tooth for a tooth? It's simple, breathe in, breathe out, judgment.
ようやく今晩無礼講 決行です
Finally, tonight, an informal gathering will be carried out.
皆様ナンセンス 甚だナンセンス
Everyone is nonsense, utterly nonsense!
イキる勿れ 黙れ 黙れ
Don't act big, shut up, shut up!
この世はナンセンス 誠に遺憾です
This world is nonsense, truly regrettable.
お気の毒ね 哀れ 哀れ 仕方ねぇ
How unfortunate, pitiful, pitiful, it can't be helped.
ほら 精々気張っていってらっしゃい
Look, try your absolute best and off you go.
じゃ 閻魔によろしく言っといて
Well then, say hello to King Yama for me.
まさに宣言通り
Just as I declared,
Dirty dirty night
右も左もどん詰まり
A dead end to the left and right,
浮ついたチェックメイト
a frivolous checkmate.
いよいよ今晩ブレイクお披露目です
Tonight is finally the big reveal!
皆様ナンセンス
Ladies and gentlemen, nonsense,
甚だナンセンス
extremely nonsense!
気休めなかれ
No room for empty comfort,
黙れ 黙れ 黙れ
shut up, shut up, shut up!
この世はナンセンス
This world is nonsense,
誠にカンゲキです
truly spectacular!
気の毒ね
What a pity,
暴れ 暴れ
run wild, run wild!
Can't you understand?
Yeah yeah Yeah yeah Yeah yeah Yeah yeah
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah...
皆様ナンセンス
Ladies and gentlemen, nonsense,
甚だナンセンス
extremely nonsense!
気休めなかれ
No room for empty comfort,
黙れ 黙れ 黙れ
shut up, shut up, shut up!
この世はナンセンス
This world is nonsense,
はなからナンセンス
nonsense from the very start!
気休めなかれ
No room for empty comfort,
黙れ 黙れ 黙れ
shut up, shut up, shut up!
まもなく時間です
Time is almost up,
誠にカンゲキです
truly spectacular!
お気は済んだ？
Are you satisfied now?
下がれ 下がれ
Back off, back off,
くたばれ
and drop dead!
ほら 精々 散々 行ってらっしゃい
Now, do your best and get lost!
満身創痍 散々 散っていきな
Covered in wounds, just fade away!
Rest in Peace
ご冥福を
my deepest condolences,
来世で逢おう
see you in the next life,
See you again
うわ！びっくりした、危な！
Whoa! You scared me, that was close!
危ないじゃないですか！
That's dangerous, you know!
何？その動き。お前、ダンサー？
What are those moves? Are you a dancer?
え？ダンサーですけど。
Huh? Yes, I am a dancer.
うわっ、私も！ダンサーです！
Whoa, me too! We're dancers!
えっ、なんかすごいダンサーがいっぱい出てきた！
Whoa, a bunch of awesome dancers just appeared!
ちょっ、えっ？
Wait, what?
なんかつら、はじめちゃんダンスのオーディション落ちちゃってさ
It's so sad... Hajime-chan failed the dance audition.
もしかして、あそこのシアターですか？
By any chance, was it at that theater over there?
そう！
Yes!
え？それ私も落ちました！
What? I failed that one too!
えー！僕も！私も！私も！みんな落ちた仲間？！
What?! Me too! Me too! Me too! So we all failed together?!
うん！ねー！
Yeah! Right?!
あのミニ番長審査員センスないよね！
That mini-bancho judge has zero taste, right?!
ねー！ほんとに！信じられない！ねー！
Exactly! Seriously! Unbelievable! Right?!
こちらのダンス、ちゃんと見せつけてやろうじゃ！
Let's show them what our dancing is really made of!
おー！
Yeah!
もう壁とは踊らないぞ！一席いくよっ！
I won't just dance with walls anymore! Let's start the show!
3メートルの覇気！こぼ・かなえる！
Three meters of Haki! Kobo Kanaeru!
カオスに満ちる、ハコス・ベールズ！
Filled with chaos, Hakos Baelz!
宇宙一の番長になる！轟はじめ！
Becoming the number one bancho in the universe! Todoroki Hajime!
よし！うちらの始まりは...
Alright! Our beginning starts...
こっから！！！
From here!!!
えー、皆さん、いくぞ！
Alright everyone, let's go!
Hey! 1, 2, 1, 2... 産声を上げな 行き先はこうだ
Hey! 1, 2, 1, 2... Cry out your birth cry! This is our destination!
生真面目いかが？如何様にして勝つ？
How about some earnestness? How will you win?
深く深く眠る凝り固まる感情を剥がせますか？
Can you peel away the deep-seated, frozen emotions?
知るか乗るか反るかしかめっ面世の中
Who cares, take a chance, sink or swim, in this frowning world,
確かな価値観の泥沼から
stuck in a swamp of fixed values.
怒鳴ったってこの葛藤で
Even if I scream, through this inner conflict...
生まれたて己の格闘で生きよう
I'll live fighting with my newly born self!
空いた穴を埋めたいの？ 愛の？愛の？
Do you want to fill the void? With love? With love?
この不協和音を愛したいの？したいの？
Do you want to love this dissonance? Do you?
これだけじゃやれねぇって分かってる
I know I can't make it with just this,
でもこれしかねぇからこれにかかってる
but this is all I have, so everything depends on it.
間違ってる未来でも俺には光ってる
Even if it's a mistaken future, it shines for me.
Ready, fire!
燃やすこの闘志 その手透かし
Burning this fighting spirit, seeing through it,
ぶっ壊したってどうしようもないままが自分なんだ
even if I break it down, this helpless self is who I am!
こっから始まんだ
It all starts from here!
いつかの等身もって努力し
Striving with the stature of that future self,
夢と相思相愛になれるはずなんだ
we're bound to fall in mutual love with our dreams!
こっから始まんだ
It all starts from here!
1 2 3 4 順番通り
1, 2, 3, 4, in perfect order,
言ってらんないだけで予定通り
just unable to say it, but everything is on track.
Rollin' Rollin' 転がって行けよ
Rollin', Rollin', keep on rolling on,
Yoly Yoly 緑の一生
Yoly, Yoly, a life of green.
1 2 3 4 順番通り
1, 2, 3, 4, in perfect order,
言ってらんないだけで予定通り
just unable to say it, but everything is on track.
Rollin' Rollin' 転がって行けよ
Rollin', Rollin', keep on rolling on,
こっから始まんだ
It all starts from here!
ええ こっからこっから
Yeah, from here, from here!
わからんだって 燃料にすれば すっからかん
If we use our confusion as fuel, we'll run completely dry!
カラッカンを落下ンスカンスカン 奴はまさに難関
A dry can falling down, down, down, that guy is truly a major obstacle!
一人になりたくても人だらけ されど気立つのは一苦労なワケ
Even if I want to be alone, it's crowded, but standing out is quite a chore.
惹かれたくないされどピープル
I don't want to draw attention, yet we're people,
でもどこいたって ピポピポピポ
but wherever we go, it's beep-beep-beep!
キーはC、ずっとC
The key is C, always C,
四苦八苦した先は荒れたレッドカーペット
and past all the struggles lies a rough red carpet.
ハハ、たりらりらりらだった、カモン！
Haha, it was just nonsense, come on!
よりどり緑ってさっき言ったろ？
Didn't I just tell you there's plenty of green?
アップダウンと無風 心の雨雲
Ups and downs with no wind, the rain clouds in my heart,
生きたる事が生きてる証拠
simply living is proof of being alive!
しかし悔しさで黒く燃える腹ん中
Yet, inside my stomach burns a dark frustration.
燃やせ！燃やせ！燃やせ！
Burn it! Burn it! Burn it!
燃やすこの闘志 その手透かし
Burning this fighting spirit, seeing through it,
ぶっ壊したってどうしようもないままが自分なんだ
even if I break it down, this helpless self is who I am!
こっから始まんだ
It all starts from here!
いつかの等身もって努力し
Striving with the stature of that future self,
夢と相思相愛になれるはずんだ
we're bound to fall in mutual love with our dreams!
こっから始まんだ
It all starts from here!
1 2 3 Let's go!
Take it to the bridge!
「俺、悪くない。なんも間違ってない」 自分じゃない何かのせいにしたい
I'm not at fault, nothing's wrong. I want to blame it on something other than me.
天才じゃないの ダッセわかんなさい
I'm not a genius, it's uncool, realize it already!
これフィクションじゃない よく見なさい 天賦の才などない
This is not fiction, look closely, there is no natural talent.
でもやめられないみたい
But I can't seem to stop.
あたしゃ阿呆か 馬鹿みたい
Am I a fool? I look like an idiot.
天才 こっから メラメラ まだまだ 自分で決めつけんな限界
Genius? From here, burning hot, don't set your own limits yet!
探せお前の正解 本当の自分なんて居やしねぇよ
Find your own answer, there is no such thing as your 'true self'!
高くならなきゃダメ 低くてはダメ って思い込んでることこそがダメ
Thinking 'it must be high, it can't be low' is what's bad.
好きこそ物の上手なれで 次こそ終える根比べ
What one likes, one will do well; next time will be the end of this test of endurance.
I can't be someone else, oh I know, I know...
このブレーキを壊したいの したいの
I want to break this brake, I want to.
足の向く方に 迷わずに動け
Move without hesitation in the direction your feet point.
道なき道ほど進め
Advance especially down pathless roads.
魂と 魂と 魂となる燃料
Our souls will become the fuel.
Let it fire!
燃やすこの闘志 その鉄格子 ぶち壊し
Burning this fighting spirit, breaking those iron bars.
どうしようもないままが 自分なんだ こっから始まんだ
Helpless as I am, that's who I am. It starts from here!
いつかの童心もって 努力し 夢と相思相愛になれるはずなんだ
Holding onto childhood innocence, working hard, we can surely fall in love with our dreams.
こっから、こっから始まんだ
From here, it starts from here.
1, 2, 3, 4 順番通り 行ってないだけで 予定通り
1, 2, 3, 4, just because it's not in order doesn't mean it's not as planned.
ローリン ローリン 転がってけ よりどりみどりの一生
Rollin', rollin', keep on rolling, a life full of endless choices.
1, 2, 3, 4 順番通り 行行行 行ってないだけで 予定通り（予定通り）
1, 2, 3, 4, just because it's not in order doesn't mean it's not as planned.
ローリン ローリン 転がってけ yo
Rollin', rollin', keep on rolling.
こっから始まんだ
It starts from here!
数年後
A few years later
Ah, ah... Ah, ah...
I can’t see what’s behind those eyes
Just wait, talk a little before they’re right
誰かの理想像に
To someone else’s ideal image
耳を傾けてしまったの
I tilted my ear
I can't take it back, no more
I guess it’s too late to call it off
感情の無い世界に溺れてさ
Drowning in a world without emotion
Tell me who I’m supposed to be
I’m lost without your honesty
I’m stuck between yes and no, oh, oh
Don't let me down
This is what you came for 狂ったように舞いな
This is what you came for, dance like you're crazy
舞いな、舞いな
Dance, dance...
said you wanna be a superstar
Show me you won’t break and fall apart
Ah, ah... Ah, ah...
Take me higher, higher
Show me you won’t break and fall apart
何かを言おうとして
Trying to say something
間違い探しのスタート合図
The starting signal of finding mistakes
Why’s everybody’s eyes on me?
慣れてしまうものね 視線の的
I’m getting used to it, the target of the gaze
I can't take it back, no more
I guess it’s too late to call it off
感じるプレッシャーは押し殺してさ
Suppressing the pressure I feel
Tell me, who I’m supposed to be?
I’m lost without your honesty
いい子気取りじゃ no, no, no
Pretending to be a good kid, no, no, no
Don't let me down
This is what you came for 狂ったように舞いな
This is what you came for, dance like you're crazy
舞いな、舞いな
Dance, dance...
said you wanna be a superstar
Show me you won’t break and fall apart
Ah, ah... Ah, ah...
Take me higher, higher
Show me you won’t break and fall apart
Yeah, said you wanna be a superstar so show me what you got
I can't take it back, no more
I guess it’s too late to call it off
感情の無い世界に溺れてさ
Drowning in a world without emotion
Tell me, who I’m supposed to be?
I’m lost without your honesty
I’m stuck between yes and no
Don't let me down
This is what you came for 狂ったように舞いな
This is what you came for, dance like you're crazy
舞いな、舞いな
Dance, dance...
said you wanna be a superstar
Show me you won’t break and fall apart
Ah, ah...
わあ！皆さん、やったあ！ありがとう！
Waa! Everyone, we did it! Thank you!
仲間と励まし合って...
Encouraging each other with my friends...
みんなから勇気をもらって...
getting courage from everyone...
こうしてステージに立って、たくさんの人の前でパフォーマンスすることができました！ありがとうございました！
and standing on the stage like this, I was able to perform in front of so many people! Thank you so much!
そして、なんと！Xトレンド1位！ありがとうございます！
And also, incredibly, #1 on X trend! Thank you so much!
そして、チャンネル登録者様も、120万人様にいったみたいで、本当にありがとうございます！
And also, it seems like our subscriber count has reached 1.2 million! Thank you very, very much!
わあ！嬉しい！
Waa! I'm so happy!
こうしてね、こう夢を追いかけて、上京して、こう、たくさんの人のスターになることができました！轟はじめです！
Chasing my dream and moving to Tokyo, I was able to become a star for so many people! I'm Todoroki Hajime!
でも、この物語を作るにあたって、たくさんの素敵なアーティストちゃんの楽曲をお借りして、あの、作ることができましたので、本当にありがとうございます！
But in making this story, we were able to borrow songs from many wonderful artists to make this, so thank you so much!
はじめも、曲をたくさん作れるように、頑張ります！
Hajime will also do her best to write lots of songs!
そして、え、これがはじめの100万人記念の新衣装になりまーす！
And, this is Hajime's new outfit commemorating 1 million subscribers!
衣装の名前は『ボーダーコード』衣装です！市原達也さんに仕立てていただきました！
The name of the outfit is 'Border Code'! It was tailored by Tatsuya Ichihara!
皆さんね、応援してくれたおかげです！ありがとうございます！
It's all thanks to everyone's support! Thank you so much!
で、今回の新衣装、髪がロング、そして、足がなんか、すごく長く見えるデザインで...
And for this new outfit, the hair is long, and the design makes my legs look really long...
ほら、セクシーな美脚！
Look, sexy beautiful legs!
どう？皆さん、なんかおかしくない？ピョコピョコがない！嘘だ、そんなバカな！そんなバカな！ピョコピョコがないだと？
What do you think? Everyone, isn't something strange? My hair wiggles are gone! No way, that's impossible! That's impossible! The hair wiggles are gone?
うわあ、嘘です！ピョコピョコもあります！わあ！ま、ピョコピョコないと脳みそ出ちゃうからね。必要だよね。
Whoa, just kidding! I have the hair wiggles too! Yay! Well, if I don't have the wiggles, my brains would spill out. They are necessary, right?
であと、ジャケットも脱げます！ほら！ほらセクシー！うわあ！詳しくはこの後のメンゲンで紹介するので、気になる方は見に来てください！
And also, I can take off the jacket! Look! Look, sexy! Whoa! I'll introduce the details in the member-only stream after this, so if you're interested, please come watch!
続いて、なんと！新曲を披露しようと思います！皆さん、盛り上がる準備できてますか？うおーい！
And next, guess what! I'm going to perform my new song! Everyone, are you ready to get hyped? Whooo!
ロング可愛い？ありがとう！
Long hair is cute? Thank you!
とてもね、かっこよくて、なんかセクシーな感じの曲になっているので、ぜひ、聴いてください！それでは、行きます！『Deep Dive』！
It's a really cool and somewhat sexy song, so please listen to it! Well then, here we go! "Deep Dive"!
Midnight 今夜は Lost my color, loose
Midnight, tonight, lost my color, loose
Baby 救い出してよ Let's get muddy
Baby, rescue me, let's get muddy
足元から つま先 際立ってる
From the feet to the toes, standing out
OK my ladies, I need you to show me
Well, magic gorgeous stance, you look so badass
Scream, scream, scream, scream and shout, hey!
Me and my girls, me and my girls
見てよ We are amazing, we are so amazing
Look at us, we are amazing, we are so amazing
Me and my girls, me and my girls
ここからだ Yes, on my way
Here we go from now, yes, on my way
Dive, let's deep dive / I wanna deep dive / Dive, yeah deep dive
Dive, let's deep dive / I wanna deep dive / Dive, yeah deep dive / Let's get out of the town
Yeah, you're looking like that girl
街中騒がす My sonic queen, hot queen, hot queen
Stirring up the town, my sonic queen, hot queen, hot queen
Yeah, you're looking like that girl
街中騒がす My sonic queen, hot queen, hot queen
Stirring up the town, my sonic queen, hot queen, hot queen
Boss talk, best dog, the star-caller
The venomous, the hardcore
まばゆい光 so shiny, 街が欲してる I'm baddie
Dazzling light, so shiny, the town wants it, I'm a baddie
Calm down するなもっと party, Ooh la la, ooh la la!
Don't calm down, party more, Ooh la la, ooh la la!
視線はコントロール, Out of my mind
Controlling your gaze, out of my mind
誰かの暴走, I don't need no more
Someone's wild rampage, I don't need no more
Wow magic gorgeous stance, you look so badass / Scream, scream, scream, scream and shout, hey!
Gimme gimme show time
Turn it up now, make up!
Are you ready? Are you ready, ready let it go?
Me and my girls, me and my girls
We gotta we gotta we gotta...
Let's get back to beat, you're my hot queen!
Dive, let's deep dive / I wanna deep dive
Dive, your deep dive
Dive, your deep dive / Let's get it, are you ready? Let's go!
Girl, you look like that girl
Girl, what you have is so hot
まさに Queen, hot Queen, hot Queen
Just like a Queen, hot Queen, hot Queen
Girl, you look like that girl
Girl, what you have is so hot
まさに Queen, hot Queen, hot Queen
Just like a Queen, hot Queen, hot Queen
はい！ということで、生誕グッズが出ました！
Alright! So, my birthday merchandise is out!
轟はじめ誕生日記念2026、フルセットはこんな感じです！
Todoroki Hajime Birthday Celebration 2026, the full set looks like this!
一つずつ紹介していきやす！
Let me introduce them one by one!
一つ目！「ぷんぷんばんちょーアクリルスタンド」！
First! "Angry Bancho Acrylic Stand"!
イラストは、A5きちゃんに書いていただきました！
The illustration was drawn by A5ki-chan!
台座が二つあるので、座ってる風にも、いろんなシチュエーションでも使えます！
Since there are two bases, you can use it sitting down or in various other situations!
怒っているのがポイントです！
The key point is that she's angry!
二つ目！「はじめとおそろいチョーカー」！
Second! "Matching Choker with Hajime"!
はじめの新衣装とおそろいのチョーカーです！
This is a choker matching Hajime's new outfit!
星のチャームがかわいい！
The star charm is so cute!
「首のサイズが合わないよ」っていう方は、おカバンなどに付けてください！
If you're like, "My neck size doesn't match," please attach it to your bag!
三つ目！「BANCHOジャージ」！
Third! "BANCHO Jersey"!
裏面のイラストは、おもちチャウダーちゃんに書いていただきました！
The illustration on the back was drawn by Omochi Chowder-chan!
表面は刺繍になってます！
The front features embroidery!
スバル先輩の生地がとても良かったので、おなじのにしていただきました！
Subaru-senpai's jersey material was so good, I got them to use the same one!
最後！「ぬいぐるみキーホルダー ブラックオーロラ衣装ver.」！
Last! "Plushie Keyholder Black Aurora Outfit ver."!
はじめて出したミニぬいぐるみの新衣装バージョンです！
It's the new outfit version of the first mini plushie we released!
「あの時買えなかったよ」っていう方、ぜひお迎えしてください！
If you're like, "I couldn't buy it back then," please bring one home!
そして、フルセット特典はこちら！
And here is the full set bonus!
今回のライブのチケット風カード！
A ticket-style card from this concert!
全員に直筆サインを書かせていただきやす！
I will be hand-signing it for everyone!
去年のね、ライブでたくさんグッズを買っていただいたおかげで、
Thanks to everyone buying so much merch at last year's concert,
今年もこんなに力を入れることができました！
we were able to put so much effort into it again this year!
ありがとうございやす！
Thank you so much!
今回のライブも楽しんでいただけただろうか？
I hope you've been enjoying today's concert as well!
生誕グッズもお迎えしていただけると、今後の励みになりやす！
Bringing these birthday goods home with you will encourage me greatly in the future!
よろしくお願いいたしやす！
Thank you for your support!
以上、グッズ紹介でした！
That's all for the merchandise introduction!
よーし、みなさん！
Alright, everyone!
このあとラストスパート！
Up next is the final spurt!
いっしょに盛り上がっていってください！いきやすよ！
Let's pump it up together! Here we go!
えーえーおー！はい！はい！
Yeah, yeah, oh! Yes! Yes!
あー！
Ah!
うわー！みんなー！ありがとうー！
Wow! Everyone! Thank you!
はぁー！みなさんありがとうございます！
Whew! Thank you so much, everyone!
それでは、今回のライブに携わってくださった方をご紹介していきたいと思います！
Now, I'd like to introduce the people who helped make this live performance happen!
まずは、ダンサー！ゆめにゃ！
First up, the dancers! Yumenya!
ちおりゃ！
Chioria!
みなみゃ！
Minamya!
そら！
Sora!
ありがとう！そして、この場にはいないんですけど、振付師の、みゆきにじま先生！
Thank you! And, though she couldn't be here today, our choreographer, Miyuki Nijima-sensei!
タップの、あか先生！
Aka-sensei for tap dancing!
ポッピン、とど先生！
Todo-sensei for poppin'!
ダンス監修、ゆか先生！
Yuka-sensei for dance supervision!
ボーカル監修、まりえ先生！
Marie-sensei for vocal supervision!
そして、ゲストにお越しいただきました、
And we also had special guests join us!
ほちまちついじちゃん、はこしゅべーるずちゃん、いちゃきりりかちゃん、みずみやちゅーちゃん！
Hoshimachi Suisei-chan, Hakos Baelz-chan, Ichijou Ririka-chan, and Mizumiya Chuu-chan!
本当にありがとうございました！
Thank you so much!
そして、今見えない中で稼働してくださってるスタッフの皆さん！
And to all the staff members working hard behind the scenes!
そして、はじめの目の前にいてくれてる、見てくれた皆さん、本当にありがとうございました！
And to everyone right here in front of me and watching, thank you so very much!
ありがとうございました！
Thank you very much!
それでは、ちょっと新曲について詳しくご紹介したいなと思います！
Now, I'd like to share some more details about my new song!
改めてタイトルは、ディープ・ダイブ！
Once again, the title is "Deep Dive"!
はい！MV公開はこの配信のすぐ後です！
Yes! The MV will be released right after this stream!
音源リリースは本日の24時からとなります！皆さん、たくさん聴いていただけると嬉しいです！
The digital release will be at midnight tonight! I hope you all listen to it a lot!
さぁ、それでは、ここで、重大発表いきたいと思います！こちらの動画をご覧ください！
Now, then, it's time for a major announcement! Please take a look at this video!
轟はじめ x FILA
[On-Screen: Hajime Todoroki x FILA]
コラボ決定！！
[On-Screen: Collaboration Confirmed!!]
COMING SOON!!
[On-Screen: COMING SOON!!]
わぁー！すごい！この度、はじめとFILAちゃんのコラボが決定しゅまちた！
Wow! Incredible! I'm thrilled to announce a collaboration between Hajime and FILA!
うわぁ、嬉しい！ありがとうございます！
Wow, I'm so happy! Thank you so much!
そしてなんと、スニーカーを含むアパレルをプロデュースちゃちていただきました！
And guess what, I got to produce apparel, including sneakers!
やったー！
Yay!
はじめっぽいカラーリングを取り入れながら、男性でも女性でも似合うように意識してデザインしてみました！
I designed them with Hajime-like colors in mind, making sure they look great on both men and women!
いっちょうけんめい、はじめのこだわりを詰め込んだスニーカーにしていくので、続報を楽しみにしていてください！
I'm putting all my effort into packing these sneakers with my personal touches, so please look forward to more updates!
え、そして、今回なんと、スニーカーだけじゃなくてね、ジャージ、Tシャツと、キャップもプロデュースしゅまちた！
And this time, not just sneakers, but I also produced tracksuits, T-shirts, and caps!
え、さらに、コラボにあたって、オリジナルのコラボロゴを、FILAちゃんと作りまちた！ドどん！
Furthermore, for this collaboration, I created an original collab logo with FILA! Ta-da!
わぁ、可愛い！
Wow, so cute!
実は、このロゴ、FILAちゃんと一緒に打ち合わせをして、考えまちた、はじめ。
Actually, we had meetings with FILA to come up with this logo together!
あ、こういう感じね、実際にこう手書きをしながら打ち合わせをして、
Ah, like this! We actually had meetings while sketching it out by hand,
どの色がいいかなって、いろんな色味を出してもらって、これに決めまちた。
discussing which colors would be best, trying out various shades, and decided on this one.
あ、一目でね、こうはじめだってわかる、こうミニ番長のシルエットがいいかなと思って入れてみまちた！
I thought it'd be great to include a silhouette of Mini Bancho so you can tell it's Hajime at a single glance!
え、このロゴがね、コラボの商品にも付きまちゅ！楽しみにしててね！
And this logo will also be on the collaboration items! Please look forward to it!
え、実はね、アパレル以外にも、FILAちゃんとのコラボ商品が出ますので、皆さん詳細な情報が出るのを、ぜひお楽しみに、お待ちください！
Actually, besides apparel, there will be other collaboration items with FILA, so please stay tuned for more detailed information!
え、この後ですね、メンバー限定アンコールライブ、21時15分からありますし、
Also, after this, we have a members-only encore live stream starting at 21:15,
え、この新曲についても、いろいろ詳しく見ていければと思いますので、
and we'll be taking a closer look at this new song in detail then,
ぜひ、まだの方はチャンネル登録と通知をオンにして、メン限も入っていただけると、アンコールも一緒に楽しめてハッピーだなと思います！
so if you haven't yet, please subscribe and turn on notifications, and join the membership to enjoy the encore together!
え、おさらいをすると、
To recap,
新曲MVこの後すぐ公開、
the new song MV will be released right after this,
21時からグッズ販売、
goods sales start at 21:00,
21時15分からアンコールライブ、
the encore live stream is at 21:15,
24時新曲音源リリースです！
and the digital release is at midnight!
ありがとうね！
Thank you so much!
それでは、メン限アンコールライブでお会いしましょう！
Well then, see you all at the members-only encore live!
バイバーイ！
Bye-bye!
いっぱいコメントありがとう！嬉しかった！
Thank you for all the comments! I was so happy!
あー、ありがとう！
Ah, thank you!
直す組！！
To the Naosu-gumi!!
いつもばめと楽しいを共有してくれてありがとう！
Thank you for always sharing fun times with Bame!
ばめチームが期待してくれるから、もっと変わりたい！もっと成長したいって思えるよ！
Because the Bame Team expects great things of me, it makes me want to change and grow even more!
ばめの歩みを支えてくれてありがとう♡
Thank you for supporting Bame's journey ♡
これからもばめと一緒に良い景色をみていきたいです！
I want to continue seeing wonderful sights together with Bame from now on!